Revenge has a new breed.
Muzzle: City of Wolves is a action, thriller, mystery
film directed by John Stalberg Jr..
LAPD officer Jake Rosser endeavors to lead a peaceful life
with his family and retired K-9 officer, Socks.
However, tranquility dissolves into chaos when a
gang targets them in a brutal attack.
Alongside his new K-9 partner Argos, Jake launches into a relentless
pursuit of justice, determined to protect his loved ones.
Jake Rosser, played by Aaron Eckhart.
Mia Rosser, played by Tanya van Graan.
Officer Beekman, played by Karl Thaning.
Detective Idalia Cutler, played by Nicole Fortuin.
Officer Cobb, played by Adrian Collins.
Detective Thorne, played by Hakeem Kae-Kazim.
Muzzle: City of Wolves is a 2025 American action thriller
film produced and directed by John Stalberg Jr.
and written by Jacob Michael King.
It serves as a sequel to Muzzle.
Aaron Eckhart reprises his role from the first film.
The film was released in the United States on November 14, 2025.
The tone is mind_bending and dark and intense.